<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Meredith Zielonka</title>
    <link>http://example.org/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Meredith Zielonka</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Blog 5: The Air War</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2022-10-06-blog-5-the-air-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2022-10-06-blog-5-the-air-war/</guid>
      <description>This blog is part of a series related to Gov 1347: Election Analytics, a course at Harvard University taught by Professor Ryan D. Enos.
This week, Gov 1347 is looking at the Air War: the neverending battle between campaigns to capture potential voters’ attention via television advertisements. There are different theories about the impact of campaign ads on voting preferences but both Gerber et al. and Huber and Arceneaux, our authors for the week, have discovered through their research that ads have little to no effect on voter mobilization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog 4: Incumbency</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2022-09-29-blog-4-incumbency/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2022-09-29-blog-4-incumbency/</guid>
      <description>This blog is part of a series related to Gov 1347: Election Analytics, a course at Harvard University taught by Professor Ryan D. Enos.
Introduction This week in Election Analytics, we will be incorporating incumbency and expert predictions into our existing models.
Incumbency is widely considered to have an impact in elections. In recent years, analysts have looked deeper into this, identifying two types of incumbent impact: President’s Party and district-level incumbency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Post 3: Polling</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2022-09-22-blog-post-3-polling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2022-09-22-blog-post-3-polling/</guid>
      <description>This blog is part of a series related to Gov 1347: Election Analytics, a course at Harvard University taught by Professor Ryan D. Enos.
Introduction This week in Election Analytics, the subject of discussion is Polling. How do polls impact election predictions? Are they reliable? How should they be weighed when compared to other factors like the fundamentals, or economy-based predictions? Before diving into my model and this week’s adjustments, let’s break down the work of some more experienced pollsters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blog Post 2</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2022-09-15-blog-post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2022-09-15-blog-post-2/</guid>
      <description>This blog is part of a series related to Gov 1347: Election Analytics, a course at Harvard University taught by Professor Ryan D. Enos.
Introduction This week in Election Analytics, we are talking about the economy. We are not the first to do this. It has long been theorized that the economy has an tremendous impact on election results, to the point that some predictors, like Yale professor Ray Fair, rely solely on economic variables in developing their models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Election Analytics: Blog Post 1</title>
      <link>http://example.org/post/2022-09-14-election-analytics-blog-post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/post/2022-09-14-election-analytics-blog-post-1/</guid>
      <description>This blog is part of a series related to Gov 1347: Election Analytics, a course at Harvard University taught by Professor Ryan D. Enos.
Introduction My name is Meredith Zielonka and I’m a sophomore at Harvard College studying Government, hopefully with a subfield specialization in data science. This semester, I will be assembling a blog in order to track the evolution of my predictions regarding the results of the 2022 midterms.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
